asalam alikum
nazarin tracks s
[Music]
Society Mar High
School helmet distribution
program
Helm
program project
dor
rajes
program
aess free
accident
Al
engineer contestant mlc or Ali janab say
Sultan Ahmed sahab General Secretary
General Secretary Ki or Ali janab asham
Arham sahab director uh Arna junior
college and School janab uh Shakil Ahmed
sahab director chent high school or
janab M M
Ali senior journalist
program progam Ahmed Al s Mars High
School director or
chairman
TR
so good
afternoon I am Ahmed alimin
correspondent of Mars High School this
school was established in the year
2006 now today
on 16th of December
2023 regarding the road safety program a
workshop is conducted in Mars high
school with collaboration with uh task
track s NGO which which which conduct a
this Society conducts a road safety
program in the different schools okay
I'm very much thankful to Mr Rajesh
Nimar who is the program officer of this
uh what I mean to program officer of
this uh Pro right to safety right to
safety Workshop so I'm very much
thankful to program head Mrs AR Arna Jan
who is the head of this program I'm
simultaneously I'm very much thankful to
Mr Muhammad mustan uh with his efforts
only this program has been done in the
Mars high school so I'm once again I'm
very very much thankful to Mr rajes Nar
thank you very
much uh today in our school almost 180
helmets has been distributed okay so 18
helmet distributed the program thank you
sir very good morning today we are here
uh in the Mars High School uh we are
from track Society NGO Road Safety NGO
it's a 16 years old organization we have
taken an initiative
to uh give a message into the Hyderabad
Society that plion Rider also must wear
a helmet this is because of like growing
up number of accidents in the on roads
of two wheelers actually so this
initiative has been taken up by tracks
society and the sponsors are icsa lomber
and they are sponsoring the helmets uh
for school childrens and their parents
actually at first I would like to thank
you for Marks Mars high school they have
given us this opportunity to conduct a
right to safety Workshop into the school
and we are very glad to give our
presentation into the school that we
have done a successfully of almost 980
helmets into the school and uh we have
spread out a message that plion Rider
also must wear an helmet so our main
objective of the tracks Society is to
reduce a road
accident in India because as two-
wheelers India is a biggest market for
two wheelers and uh mostly like two
wheelers based on the two wheelers
the two wheelers are not safe on the
roads so this message that like two
wheelers also must wear an helmet a
plion rider also must wear an helmet and
this initiative has been taken up
through schools so that a message
reached through schools actually so we'
like to thank you so much for giving us
opportunity and uh I especially thankful
to all the Media Group for giving us a
good coverage for into the society thank
you
kitchen home appliances or
fashion Cosmetics all Under One Roof
only 99
R only 99 Shand quality imported variety
only
99 ma Danga mura Hyderabad